¿Qué estás haciendo?
Where are you taking me?
Leave me. Help! Someone!
Help! You animals!
Enough! Drop her here!
Get up!
Hey. Hey.
Do you mind if I have a little snack?
Violence always raises my appetite.
Yeah.
Sorry, no hugs this time.
I’m afraid I might get dirty.
You’re afraid of getting dirty?!
A whole soap factory couldn’t clean
you and your slut!
Stupid rich girl.
Crawling in your own spit,
and yet still being so rude.
What’s with all the theatrics?
Bella, bravo, bravo.
So brave, so fearless, right?
No wonder my little brother
clings to you.
Even I'm curious
about playing with you
a little game.
How do you feel about
family addition?
I heard you recently became
a pure orphan.
You’re a filthy animal!
Wanna hear a little story?
Once upon a time,
my parents
offered yours a business merger.
And what did the Aspens do?
They brushed us off.!
They told us our money “smell” to them!
Fucking smell!
Get out!
Do you remember
what eventually happened
to your family?
Don't repeat their mistakes.
All I need is
a third of everything you have.
Sign over
what’s your grandfather owned.
Agree, sis.
Don’t be stubborn.
Sis?
I am no sister of yours.
Don’t touch me!
You know what, Greg?
You're even dumber than I thought.
Don't you know my
signature means nothing
without Mason’s legal consent?
You need a lawyer?
No problem.
Hey. Come here.
This is my lawyer.
And about Mason...
What?
What about Mason?
How about asking him?